# CRISTOBAL IGNACIO OLAVE **HERRERA**

Computer Civil Engineer

#### **ABOUT ME**

An organized and meticulous professional capable of coordinating multiple tasks under extreme pressure, willing to contribute to the company in order to meet the objectives that are required to succeed, while gaining experience in general in order to improve on my skills.

### **SKILLS**

• Data Management.

- Business logic.
- Production Management.
- Observant.
- Flexible.
- Requirement Analysis.
- Strong Soft Skills
- Adaptable

### **CONTACT INFO**



Capitán Danilo Vicencio 920, El Bosque, Santiago, Chile, 8030607



+56 9 5335 4720



c.olaveherrera@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ cristobal-olave-herrera-14196a156/



https://cristobalolaveherrera.we



https://github.com/COv879

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

QA NOVA

September 2023 - December 2023

QA AUTOMATION ENGINEER

Experience: Automation process designer and tester on Robomotion, also designed a learning module based on Karate Framework. Applied Tools: JavaScript, Robomotion, Karate Framework, Scrum.

LEBOX

May 2023 - August 2023

QA ANALYST

Experience: QA Tester asigned to locate, replicate and document, via jira tickets, potential bugs at the Medicap scheduling page, also designed automated Selenium tests with Python. Applied Tools: Selenium Webdriver, Postman, Insomnia, SQL (Oracle), Jira,

Scrum.

ENTIX

February 2022 - May 2022

ETL DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP)

Experience: Data transformation process designer from CSV files to an Oracle DB.

Applied Tools: Informatica Powercenter, SQL (Oracle).

• THE EARTH SAYS

May 2021 - August 2021

BACKEND DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP)

Experience: Developer on a bee counting algorithm based on YOLOV4 via docker and also developed an JSON API that conects the algorithm into a Oracle DB via Node.JS.

Applied Tools: Docker, Git, JavaScript, Node.JS.

# **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSIDAD ANDRES BELLO

2017 - 2022

Professional Title - Computer Civil Engineer.

# **LANGUAGES**



## **CERTIFICATES**

- Advanced English.
- Native Spanish.
- Basic French.
- IBM Data Science Practitioner.
- Brainnest Data Analysis Training Program.
- freeCodeCamp Data Analysis with Python

# TOOLS AND PROGRAMING LANGUAGES

- Python
- C#
- Java
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- Git
- Jira
- Django, Flask
- Node.JS, React
- Amazon Web Service

- Selenium
- · Visual Studio Code
- · Postman, Insomnia
- Office 365
- Tableau
- Jupyter Notebook
- Informatica Powercenter
- Karate Framework (Gherkin)
- Docker